RG 058, Research Commission
Connecticut State Library
- Series 7. Reading files, 1966-1971
  - Wachsman, Eileen B., 1969-1971 (Box 29)
  - Fiori, Lorry, 1970 June-1971 December (Box 29)
  - Heintz, H. F. (Box 29)
    - 1966-1969 (Box 29)
    - 1970 January-1971 (Box 30)
  - Hobbah, Reginal V., 1967-1969 (Box 30)
  - Kessler, Roland R., 1967-1971 (Box 30)
  - LeCompte, Gare, 1968-1971 (Box 30)
  - McKee, Clyde D., 1968 (Box 30)
  - White, Robert N., 1969-1971 (Box 30)
- Series 8. Press Releases, 1966-1970
  - Records, 1966-1970 (Box 30)
- Series 9. General file, 1965-1971
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Annual reports, 1967-1969 (Box 31)
  - Blue Book requests, 1966 (Box 31)
  - Budget, 1965-1968 (Box 31)
  - Conference - Fairfield, 1968 (Box 31)
  - Conference - Research Directors, 1968 (Box 31)
  - Conference - Technological Innovation, 1968 (Box 31)
  - Conference, 1968 (Box 31)
  - Directory of research labs (Box 31)
  - Hobbah, R. V. (Box 32)
  - Inquiries pre-approval, 1966-1970 (Box 32)
  - Job inquiries (Box 32)
  - Laboratory Techinicians Project (Box 32)
  - Library - CRC (Box 32)
  - Meeting with industry, 1966 September 12 (Box 32)
  - Proposal completion, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - Proposal statistics, 1965-1969 (Box 32)
  - Publicity, 1966-1969 (Box 32)
  - Report of activities, 1967 (Box 32)
  - Security clearances (Box 32)
  - State Teechnical Services Act (Box 33)
  - STSP - Activities of other states (Box 33)
  - STSA - Advisory Council (Box 33)
  - STS - Conference (Box 33)
  - STS - New England Technical Services (Box 33)
  - STSA - Information bulletins (Box 33)
  - STSA - Internal members (etc.) (Box 33)
  - STSA - Regional Coordinating Committee (Box 33)
  - STSA - Regional Legal (Box 33)
  - STSA - Regional Plan NEERF (Box 33)
  - STSA - Regional plan other states (Box 33)
  - STSA - State plan info (Box 33)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce (Box 33)
  - Unman, Carolita (Box 33)
- Series 10. Financial files, 1964-1969
  Arranged by fiscal year, thereunder by type of document.
  - 1964-1965 (Box 34)
    - Receipts (Box 34)
  - 1965-1966 (Box 34)
    - Allotments (Box 34)
    - Commitment lists (Box 34)
    - Budget (Box 34)
    - Payment lists (Box 34)
    - Reservation of funds (Box 34)
    - Subscriptions (Box 34)
    - Transfer invoices (Box 34)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 34)
    - Allotments (Box 34)
    - Appropriations statement (Box 34)
    - Budget (Box 34)
    - Commitment lists (Box 34)
    - Expenditure statements (Box 34)
    - Payment lists (Box 34)
    - Requisition for reservation of funds (Box 34)
    - Service transfer invoices (Box 34)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 34)
    - Allotments (Box 34)
    - Appropriation statements (Box 34)
    - Budget (Box 34)
    - Commitment lists (Box 34)
    - Expenditure statemetns (Box 34)
    - Paid invoices (Box 34)
    - Requisition for reservation of funds (Box 35)
    - Service transfer invoices (Box 35)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 35)
    - Allotments (Box 35)
    - Appropriation statements (Box 35)
    - Allotments (Box 35)
    - Commitment lists (Box 35)
    - Expenditure statements (Box 35)
    - Paid invoices (Box 35)
    - Payment list expenditure certificates list of invoices (Box 35)
    - Requisition for reservation of funds (Box 35)
    - Service transfer invoices (Box 35)
    - Service transfer lists (Box 35)